Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Conventions
  - Forty-Fifth: Constitutional Amendments, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Forty-Fifth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Forty-Fifth: Delegates, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Forty-Fifth: EEOC Reports, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Forty-Fifth: Election, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Forty-Fifth: Resolutions, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Forty-Sixth: Agenda, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Forty-Sixth: Constitutional Amendments, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Forty-Sixth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Forty-Sixth: First Caucus, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Forty-Sixth: Second Caucus, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Forty-Sixth: Delegates, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Forty-Sixth: Elections, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Forty-Sixth: Resolutions, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Forty-Seventh: Agenda, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Forty-Seventh: First Caucus, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Forty-Seventh: Second Caucus, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Forty-Seventh: Constitutional Amendments, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Forty-Seventh: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Forty-Seventh: Delegates, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Forty-Seventh: Delegate Nominating Committee, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Forty-Seventh: Elections, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Forty-Seventh: Plenary Sessions, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Forty-Seventh: Post Convention Correspondence, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Forty-Seventh: Resolutions, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Forty-Eighth: Agenda, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Forty-Eighth: Committees, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Forty-Eighth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Forty-Eighth: First Caucus, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Forty-Eighth: Second Caucus, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Forty-Eighth: Delegates, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Forty-Eighth: EEOC Reports, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Forty-Eighth: Elections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Forty-Eighth: Pension and Welfare Report Transcript, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Forty-Eighth: Plenary Session, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Forty-Eighth: Resolutions, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Forty-Ninth: Agenda, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Forty-Ninth: Constitutional Amendments, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Forty-Ninth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Forty-Ninth: Delegates, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Forty-Ninth: Elections, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Forty-Ninth: Financial Documents, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Forty-Ninth: Resolutions, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Fiftieth: Agenda, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Fiftieth: First Caucus, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Fiftieth: Second Caucus, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Fiftieth: Constitutional Amendments, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Fiftieth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Fiftieth: Delegates, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Fiftieth: Election, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Fiftieth: EEOC Reports, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Fiftieth: Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Fiftieth: Post Convention Caucus, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Fiftieth: Resolutions, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Fifty-First: Agenda, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Fifty-First: First Caucus, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Fifty-First: Second Caucus, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Fifty-First: Third Caucus, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Fifty-First: Fourth Caucus, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Fifty-First: Constitutional Amendments, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Fifty-First: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Fifty-First: Delegates, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Fifty-First: Elections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Fifty-First: Executive Conference, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Fifty-First: National Board Plenary Session, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Fifty-First: Post Convention Caucus, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Fifty-First: Resolutions, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Fifty-Second: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Fifty-Second: Elections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Fifty-Second: Executive Conference, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Fifty-Second: National Board Plenary Committee, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Fifty-Second: Presidents Committee, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Fifty-Third: Executive Conference, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Series V: Charges, Claims, and Arbitrations
  Files are arranged alphabetically.
  One of AFTRA's major functions as a union is to defend the rights and protections of its members. This series documents many of these cases, including those concerning pension, insurance, welfare claims, wrongful termination, protections for freelancers, contract violations, insufficient compensation, grievance procedures, and violations of collective bargaining rights. Particularly well represented in this series are AFTRA's cases against the Inner City Broadcasting Corporation and Tuesday Productions, as well as charges resulting from the 1981 National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET) strike. In addition to individual cases, the series demonstrates the larger issue of the right of the union to limit its members to working only under a union contract. Also included in this series are materials from binders entitled, "Monies Collected by AFTRA on Behalf of its Members."
  - ABC: Newsperson's Claims, 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - ABC Incorporated: Paper Complaint, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - ABC: Pension and Welfare Claims, 1978-1982 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - ABC v. Mel Brandt, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Abrams-Rubaloff and Associates Inc. v. Katherine Breech, Susan Lucci, and Ruth Warrick, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA: Arbitrations/Hearing Dates, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA v. 1430 Associates: Termination of Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA v. 1430 Associates: Termination of Staff, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA v. 1430 Associates: Unfair Labor Practice, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Additional Compensation, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "All My Children", 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Deidra Boumauro, 1976-1982 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: William Crowley, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Freelance Newspersons' Backfees WABC and WPLJ, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Freelance Newspersons' Backfees WABC and WPLJ, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Freelance Newspersons' Backfees WABC and WPLJ, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Freelance Newspersons' Backfees WABC and WPLJ, Financial Statement, 1969-1981 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Freelance Newspersons' Backfees WABC and WPLJ, Logs and Schedules, 1968-1981 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Dirk Fredericks, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Katherine Glass, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Robert Gibson, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Robert Gibson, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Hunter, Miller, Gibson, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: In-Hire Rate, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "Kids are People Too", 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "Kids are People Too", 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Lateness Provision, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "Live in Studio" Rates, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Robert Miller, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Mini Cameras, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: NCAA Football, 1979-1982 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: News Anchors Compensation, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: News Anchors Compensatory Days, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Newsmen's Fees, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "One Life to Live", 1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Pension and Welfare for Soap Operas, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Pension and Welfare for Newspersons, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "Perspective", 1980 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Promos, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Ruth Redfern, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "Seven Around Town", 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Termination of Michael McKay, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: "Three's Company", 1981 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - AFTRA v. ABC: Cheryl Tiegs, Erma Bombeck, Sylvia Feldman, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA v. ABC, NBC, and CBS, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA v. ABC, NBC, and CBS, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA v. ABC, NBC, and CBS, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA v. ABC Records: Frankie Lane, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA v. Bartell Broadcasters, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA v. Batten, Baron, Durstine, and Osborn: Delta Airlines Commercial, 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA v. Black Tie Network, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA v. Black Tie Network, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA v. BMR Concepts Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA v. BMR Concepts Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA v. Botsford, Ketchum Inc., 1975 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - AFTRA v. Brown, Himan, 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - AFTRA v. Brownstone Productions: Sondra Lee, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - AFTRA v. Brownstone Productions: Sondra Lee, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - AFTRA v. Calandra Productions, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - AFTRA v. Capital Cities Communications, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Appropriation of Fees, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: John Bohannan, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: John Derr, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: David Leslie Gibson, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: "Love is a Many Splendored Thing", 1969 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Gary Maurer, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Meal Periods for "Love is a Many Splendid Thing", 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Mini Cameras, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Modification of Employment Contract for Television Program, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Gene Moss, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Palmer Payne, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Radio Programming Services, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Segments of Stage Shows, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Stage Shows on News Programs, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: Stock Purchase Plan and Sick Leave, 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: WCBS Newsmen, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - AFTRA v. CBS: WEEI Radio Boston, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - AFTRA v. CBS Records: Contractor Issues, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - AFTRA v. CBS Records: Christine Spencer, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - AFTRA v. CBS, V and R Advertising, and Len Carl Advertising, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - AFTRA v. Charles Fries Productions, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - AFTRA v. Claire Malis, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - AFTRA v. Columbia Pictures Industries: "Fish", 1979 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - AFTRA v. Combined Communications Corporations, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - AFTRA v. Community Group for New Jersey Radio Inc: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - AFTRA v. Community Group for New Jersey Radio Inc: Legal Documents, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - AFTRA v. Dan Curtis Productions, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - AFTRA v. Debs Memorial Fund, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - AFTRA v. Dow Jones and Company, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - AFTRA v. Ed Marshall Productions: Deborah Lynn, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - AFTRA v. Educational Broadcasting Corporation, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - AFTRA v. Elkins Productions International, 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - AFTRA v. FM Broadcasting Corporation: Contract Violation, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - AFTRA v. FM Broadcasting Corporation: Staff Announcers of WHLI, 1953-1959 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - AFTRA v. The Forward Association: Danny Stiles, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - AFTRA v. GAF Broadcasting Company: Robert Adams, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA v. GAF Broadcasting Company, re: Joseph Marzano and Leslie Rubenstein, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - AFTRA v. General Teleradio, 1952-1957 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - AFTRA v. Gilbert Broadcasting Corporation, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - AFTRA v. Golnick Company, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - AFTRA v. Griswold-Eshleman Company, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - AFTRA v. GWB Productions, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - AFTRA v. Hartig-Josephson Agency, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - AFTRA v. Henderson/Hogan Agency: "All My Children", 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - AFTRA v. John Hoffman: Kim Production, Fresh Faces, and Endorsements Now, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - AFTRA v. Hope Enterprises, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Charges, Mar 1983-Nov 1984 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Jul 1984 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, Aug-Dec 1984 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Decision, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Decision, Feb 7, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Decision, Feb 10, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Exhibits, 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Exhibits, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Exhibits, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Exhibits, 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Exhibits, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Jan-Feb 1982 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Mar 1983 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Apr-Jun 1983 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Jul 1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Aug 1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Sep 1983 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Jan-May 1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, Jun-Dec 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Handwritten Notes, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: LaMarr Howard Severance, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 8A)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Judge Lowe Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, 1978-1982 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Jan-Feb 1984 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Mar-Jun 1984 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Jul-Dec 1984 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Jan-Aug 1985 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Oct-Nov 1985 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Jan-Mar 1986 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Legal Documents, Apr-Oct 1986 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Negotiations, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Negotiations, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Negotiations, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: P&W Reports, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Research Materials, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Research Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Research Materials, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Research Materials, 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, Apr 9, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, May 23, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, May 21, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, May 22, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, May 23, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, May 24, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, Jul 8, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, Jul 9, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, Jul 10, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, Jul 11, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - AFTRA v. Inner City Broadcasting/Inner City v. AFTRA: Transcript, Jul 12, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - AFTRA v. International Teleview, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - AFTRA v. Ira Barmak Productions, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - AFTRA v. Ira Barmak Productions, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - AFTRA v. J. Walter Thompson USA, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - AFTRA v. Jamur Productions, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - AFTRA v. Jay-Bar Industries, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - AFTRA v. Judick Broadcasting Company, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA v. JWT Productions: "Slim Goodbody", 1978-1981 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA v. JWT Productions: "Slim Goodbody", 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA v. KHQ Incorporated, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA v. KIXI AM-FM, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA v. The Kleinman Company: "The Passion of Dracula", 1979 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA v. The Kleinman Company: "The Passion of Dracula", 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA v. The Kleinman Company: "The Passion of Dracula", 1983 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA v. KPIX: Maralee Jane Beck, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA v. KPNX Broadcasting Company, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA v. Lake Champlain Broadcasting Corporation: Bargaining Representatives, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA v. Lake Champlain Broadcasting Corporation: Working Conditions, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - AFTRA v. Lake Champlain Broadcasting Corporation: Unfair Labor Practices, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - AFTRA v. Lawrence Weiner and Associates: Arbitrator's Bill, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968-1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973-1982 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Legal Documents, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Legal Documents, Jan-Jul 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Legal Documents, Aug-Dec 1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Legal Documents, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Oct 26, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Nov 3, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Apr 6, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Jun 6, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Jun 19, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Jul 3, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - AFTRA v. Lewis, Irving: Transcripts, Deposition, Jul 9, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - AFTRA v. Loew's, 1955-1959 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - AFTRA v. Manchester Broadcasting Productions, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA v. Manchester Broadcasting Productions, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA v. Manchester Broadcasting Productions, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA v. Maravilla Production Company: "Good Night America", 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA v. Maravilla Production Company: "Good Night America", 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA v. Marstellar, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA v. Metiomedia, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA v. Mongomery, Michael: "That's Show Biz", 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA v. Municipal Broadcasting System: Donald Blair, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA v. Mutual Broadcasting System: Announcer's Agreement Violation, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA v. Mutual Broadcasting System: Harold Huber, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA v. Mutual Broadcasting System: Ivan Scott, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - AFTRA v. Mutual Broadcasting System: Texas Employees, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - AFTRA v. National General Corporation: "Play of the Week", 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 33)